sup everyone he was only three four five
here with a very special video today my
mom I just got back to Walmart what she
got like a bunch of primo cats on
selling so I thought hey you know
it'd be fine families for each other me
raising a bunch of Pringle flavors from
like best to worst and so that's
what we're gonna do today right as you
can see I got like seven I got six types
of Pringle Pringles that I'm gonna be
testing out and I'm going them from best
to worst today I've got cheddar cheese
salt and vinegar sour cream over AG good
ol original cheddar and sour cream so I
don't I know
Oh No so I guess that's DC together some
oh no that's how people onion and then
the last one I got is like ranching
which I know it's gonna be good but I
like ranch
I like Pringles BAM it's gotta be good
and like as you can see you cannot
I'm not sure you can see it behind the
peel camps but like in the backgrounds I
got like the 4th Teletubby then some
boo balls and like don't be alarmed
if it was just there for decorations and
like I was going to get my Sonic
like sock on the ground sock plushie
from Denny's and that I own but I
didn't want to get our covered in
Pringle Pringles dust and so yeah
like that's that's why that's why they
were back there for decoration but not
like any of my soccer members because I
don't want to get dirty and so oh
and when I write them out I'll probably
like let me just move the cannons when I
started like ranking them actually are
like I'll take the cans down for no
when I start wrecking them all they make
them like the best words will be over
here and like the worst ones will go
there and I like the Pringle
doesn't tell me or does that not look
like Uncle Chuck that looks like on the
truck if he was like younger
but like not like s and not not as sexy
as Uncle Chuck if you get I just knows I
got the orange one and and the green one
that's like me and dick up in this
I didn't mean for that rad
now wall good thing I have like like the
orange one like up here cuz we all know
like minis hell is orange and and
we all know how much he's a master
how about we take take a bathroom first
because I mean you just know Mindy
everybody
so I'm guessing everybody with the
Pringles cheddar cheese and I rap
so like let's let's just get this
open so I can taste it oh that smells
like there you go it's like it is
as orange as you would expect ooh now
I'll be honest I'm not a big fat cheese
but I am a big fan of Mindy cuz she's
like got big boobies so you don't know
me maybe no surprise me let's have a
take me along so pretty good me do
pretty good
I got another one that's better stop
I'll put it over like like the highest
right now it's definitely gonna go lower
cuz Mindy like cheddar cheese Pringles
you are right okay next up
we got we can go original up in this
like like I'm sorry Mindy and you
just taste like a slide like I
gotta get something like this I gotta
get something like normal and like
if if the Pringles challenge is like
around with like a hundred
people the pretty little job it's like
it's like oil and so of course I
got Tyler that's it there's no smell at
all what the
Travis that looks like a
potato oh
chips are made of potatoes that's why I
call them potato chips I just got there
I thought I thought ships were made of
bread do you learn something new every
day you know I said what I said
about the Pringles
but honestly this not as good as a
cheese sometimes you gotta just have a
so sorry original is going below
cheddar well I don't know yeah yeah the
wings this one it's going right
there no I'm going one I don't think I
like a 40 because it's like blue like
good old sock the Hedgehog like Bobby
price shutting someone up his ass cuz
you beyond we all know why it's good
I guess my mom is a fat I
seen open this morning I told in October
so I'm finna go oh oh that smells like
pickles oh I don't like this
already I'm good this gonna - ASIS woman
because I know it's gonna go the wrong
side I do not like vinegar that
that ain't doing this I need
it I only do I need to watch this ad
with no I'm going back to original just
for that that goes number one I don't
give a haven't give a
that I need water
I don't like that that is not going that
that's really beyond the list but
because it's like the whoops are putting
you at the bottom
that let's Chuck cheddar and sour
cream
I mean the it was pretty good so
maybe you were before that let's draw
yeah let's just sell frame now coming on
you let's try this I mean this is
like green like manage the Hedgehog this
has no smells Fozzie I thought its
onions put it down it's got a little
nevermind
I thought it had green on but it
didn't now this is my imagination or
some okay that's good
that's like eating if you're eating the
chip and dip he likes out coming on you
which is probably they're going for I'm
putting that top no exemption
you like this it's green like you okay I
think we're doing pretty good so let's
see blue
well why blue like Uncle Chuck let's try
this this is exactly like the sour
cream but with cheese
why does he like cheese I don't like
this
oh all right it's those two how disease
what's them a if it's shredder
cheese wait but it tastes like this and
this how could it is worse than this one
that if its bow if it's both the good
ones let's hold on she's our chair
I took me know about it was not a
good job without this good either that
she's ruled it when you taste that I'm
funny I'm putting the slug keeper
position I'll probably change that but
for now let's go to the last one rats
this is the exciting one this is what
they get inside cuz you got like a chip
with that Kakao boy had at its last wing
like some ranch and I think I can't tell
what that is like it might be some
broccoli or some it looks like
sausages sausages little green I don't
know I don't give a okay let's do
this oh fill down okay we got round
this is like this is locked the so
let's it could either be or these
but we don't know until we try
amer either one oh nothing like that I
do not like that one bit that's what the
bottom so there you go that's what's
going down
wait let me calm about it does let me
see if you liked it I'm gonna eat them
with my eyes closed
just to see which one is bad I'm gonna
eat this one I don't know what it is my
fault okay okay
nape makes me wanna put my hat
above I don't know if that's good or bad
so it's more better oh okay do full
one
okay I spit it out I spit out orange
pieces this one you're going down
adjust my friends I know that was you
the first ones better next one was the
first one so there we go I warm from
best to us we got sour cream and onion
then girl all original then cheddar sour
cream so I'm vinegar the cheddar
cheese and left plates as if as it
should be is ranch thanks everyone
thanks for watching
[Music]
we can travel back in time